♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 9x02 ♪
The Separation Oscillation
Original Air Date on September
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Skype ringing)
(Amy(on skype):)Sheldon, I don't think
you understand
(Amy(on skype):)how being broken up works.
(Amy(on skype):)The only way
I can sort through my feelings
(Amy(on skype):)is if there is space between us.
(Amy(on skype):)Every time I see you,
it re-traumatizes me.
(Amy(on skype):)I go through the pain
all over again.
(Sheldon:)Well, hello to you, too.
(Amy:)What do you want?
(Sheldon:)I understand
we're no longer a couple,
(Sheldon:)but I would like to remind you
that we made a baby together.
(Amy:)What baby?
(Sheldon:)A precocious
little Internet show
known as "Fun With Flags."
(Amy:)I'm hanging up.
(Sheldon:)Great. See you in
about half an hour.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I am not doing
"Fun With Flags" with you.
(Sheldon:)Why not?
(Amy:)Because we're broken up.
(Sheldon:)Sonny and Cher made it work.
(Sheldon:)Their variety show
kept going
(Sheldon:)long after the divorce,
(Sheldon:)and here we are
still talking about them.